{
    "subject": "resource/Barry_Van_Dyke",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Barry Van Dyke was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9316712617874146,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8694367408752441,
            "question": "Where was Barry Van Dyke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8372898101806641,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.678861677646637,
            "question": "What is Barry Van Dyke's country of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6300584077835083,
            "question": "What nationality is Barry Van Dyke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6147758960723877,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Barry Van Dyke's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5286762118339539,
            "question": "What is Barry Van Dyke's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4274936616420746,
            "question": "To which nation does Barry Van Dyke belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3896913528442383,
            "question": "In which country did Barry Van Dyke come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31840550899505615,
            "question": "Where did Barry Van Dyke spend his early years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Barry Van Dyke was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1207_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Barry Van Dyke come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1207_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which nation does Barry Van Dyke belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1207_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Barry Van Dyke's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1207_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1207_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information about Barry Van Dyke's birthplace, stating he was born in Atlanta, Georgia, USA. Therefore, the statement that Barry Van Dyke was born in the United States is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}